shanibazaaronline.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy and Disclaimer For the Term Of Use_**

We at  [WWW.Shanibazaaronlie.com](http://www.shanibazaaronlie.com/)  (here in after website, unless mentioned specifically)value the Privacy and Security of the Data that Users, Visitors, Customers (here after Known as the ‘users’). This Privacy policy applies to all the Products, services,  and the Website offered by [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/), and the Details of the users provided by the user in order to fulfill their orders an Services at demand and its disclosure.

**_Agreeing to the Terms and Conditions Mentioned here you agree to :_**

·         Your use of any part of or the whole website and the Data or any Personal Information that you provide on the website is governed by the Terms and Conditions of the **Shanibazaaronline.com.**

·         The Terms and Condition mentioned here is Only for the Website and services provided by JTS retail ([www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/)), while other websites(herein after known as third party) may be displayed on shanibazaaronline.com through various links. While being transferred from our website to third party website, we request you to go through the privacy statement of the Websites you are being redirected to.

·         We may use third party ad-services to serve and track ads on shanibazaaronline.com.  These  companies might the Information available on shaniobazaaronline.com(not including your Personal details Like your name, email, phone number etc.)

·         Any dispute will be considered under the Jurisdiction of the Delhi Court.

**_Data Collection and Its Use :_**

·         We do not require you to Login in order to check the products displayed on the Website. Registration is only required to place an order , participating in blogs, forums or to participate in the Competitions held  by Shanibazaaronline.com from time to time.

·         Shanibazaaronline.com  do collect  your Information at the Time of  Order Being Placed, when you create an account with the shanibazaaronline.com,  Or  when you participate at the Forum Discussion, competition, or share your Ideas on the website. We may provide this information to our partner channels and third parties to fulfill the service requirement you purchased or ordered.

·         Shanibazaaronline collects the non-personal information that can used to identify the user on the website and use this information to enhance you experience on our website and services.

·         We may use the information you provide for the Following purposes : to conduct research and trends of purchases and services or products mostly bought by you, for the Advertising content that you see on website, to improve the quality and provide you the best services and purchase experience, and provide anonymous reports to internal and external clientele.

·         You agree that JTS Retail will the sole owner of the Information provided by you on the website .

·         You have option to provide the non sensitive data such as birth date, gender, location in order to enhance the experience of your shopping.

·         JTS Retail collects information at various stages inside the website

**_ORDERS_**

IF you make a purchase of  products or services on shanibazaaronline.com, we will be requiring some of your personal details in order to process and complete the order. This information needs to be filled in the order form at checkout page of the website. We will also be collecting some financial  details in order to sell the Product or services offered by us. We will be using this information for the Invoicing purpose and for the Delivery of your product  and services.

**_NEWS LETTER_**

You will have an option to opt-in for our newsletter in order to know about the Latest deals and offers that we make on our website. By making an account with us or purchasing a product or service from us you give us consent to send you the marketing mails and messages. To opt out of the newsletter you  can either indicate the same on the Order form or  you can mail us on [support@shanibazaaronline.com](mailto:support@shanibazaaronline.com).

**_Childern Under 13 years of age_**

[www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/) or JTS Retail does not intentionally or otherwise collect the data of the children below 13 years of age.

**_Information sharing and Disclosure_**

Shanibazaaronline.com or JTS Retail do not sell , trade or share the Personal Information of its users with any third party until and unless it is required to do so for providing the Products and services that you purchased. We only do so with your consent or Under the unavoidable circumstances as below:

·         For delivery purpose as we use third party shipping services for the Delivery purpose. We also use third party credit card processing company to bill you for the Products and services you bought on shanibazaaronline.com. as we do take care  of the Privacy of our esteemed customers we prohibit third parties from using your information for the promotional purpose. They are Required and supposed to use the information that we provide for the services or the Intentional that we have discussed with the Third parties.

·         We do provide the non personal information  to the  interested third parties for the Research and analysis of the trending usages of the website, products and services , in order to provide you the Best experience with us.

·         We use you personal and non personal information provide by you  in order to enhance the Look and feel of the Website and to provide you and enriched experience on our website and to create advertising, creating new features, promotions, functionality by analyzing the details of the trends and preferences of the users.

·         We reserve the right to share your details and personal information that is with us if required by Law and when we see that disclosure is required in interest of [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/)  or JTS Retail/ or to comply with judicial process, or legal processed  served by our website.

·         We may also share the users personal information where we feel it is necessary to investigate , prevent or take actions against illegal activities, suspected frauds, situations involving the threat to physical safety of a person or in breach of [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/) or JTS Retail’s terms of use.

·         If  JTS Retail or [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/) goes in any business transaction such as a merger, acquisition by any other company, or sale of any part of or complete assets, Your personal information will be assets that will be likely to be transferred. You may or might not notified as fit deemed by the Acquiring company.

**_Your Ability To modify the account details :_**

IF your personal details changes or you decide to no longer maintain an account on [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/) you can modify the account details by logging in to user area of the [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/) and change the Details of your account. If you wish to delete the account then you should mail us on [support@shanibazaaronline.com](mailto:support@shanibazaaronline.com).

**_Confidentiality and Security_**

We strictly follow the Industry standards to protect the personal data of the Users that is submitted on the website, during the transaction. However no method of transmission over the web and electronic storage is 100% secure, so we strive hard to protect the Information we gather but we cannot guarantee the absolute security of the data. If you have any suggestions or questions about security of [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/) please write to us [support@shanibazaaronline.com](mailto:support@shanibazaaronline.com).

We limit the no. of employees who access your data to only those who we believe need to come in contact of such information for fulfilling the orders of products and services on our website.

The security of your personal information is our priority concern and is important to us. We use 256 bit SSL encryption to encrypt any sensitive information that you submit while ordering or while registering for the services we offer.

**_Cookies and Web Beacons_**

·         We do use both session id and persistent cookies. The session cookies makes the Navigation for users easier. We also uses session id cookie which expires as soon as you close the Browser. The Persistent cookie remain on your hard drive for a longer period of time, however you can remove the same by following the browser help file.

·         We have set a cookie to store your password. The persistent  cookie also help to track and target the users interest hence helps us to improve the overall experience on [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/)

·         You can choose to not to use cookies on your browser and still be able to navigate the website., however it will limit the use of some of website areas.

·         The use of cookies by our partners and any other third partner is not covered in this policy and terms of use.

·         When You will click on any third party link including an advertisement you will leave shanibazaaronline.com and go to that third party website and we will not accept any responsibility for the third party use of your information and they will adhere to the practice as we do.

·         **ShaniBazaarOnline.com** may use web beacons in connection with e-mails sent to  **ShaniBazaarOnline.com** users, to let us know whether and when the email was opened. No personal information is transmitted through web beacons.

**_International Users_**

International Users are users who are using the website from any part of world apart from India. Through your use you are giving consent the information to be transferred in India and the laws and regulation governing personal information and data collection is subject to Indian Laws and you give your consent to abide by the Terms and Use of the [www.shanibazaaronline.com](http://www.shanibazaaronline.com/).

**_Changes and Update to this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use_**

[www.shanibazaaronline](http://www.shanibazaaronline/) or JTS retail may update or change this policy at anytime in its sole discretion and without prior notice. We will try to notify on your primary email registered with us. However we would encourage you to visit the website’s terms of use and privacy Policy regularly for any update.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**_Contact Information_**

If you have any questions or suggestions, we would like to hear it. You can contact us on :

Email : support@shanibazaaronline.com
